[Music]
Kevin Global accelerated macro Solutions
this is Ryan hey Ryan we need your
help hey what's going on the TV is not
working I don't know what happened I me
I'm at work right now I can't talk I'll
have to I'll talk to you later no no
we're at home all day just just just
tell us how to fix
TV is it on input 4 make sure it's on
input four ask him what uh set
of set of inputs there's about a 100
inputs in the back there's about a 100
inputs in the
back put jack on the phone jack he wants
to talk to you does it look like I want
to talk to somebody no he's tied up he's
just got cords everywhere and he's
fiddling with he's fiddling with the
chords did you unplug the quarts
yeah we did how do what did you you
do how did you do this we didn't want to
call you at work so we tried to do it
ourselves well you're bothering me at
work now no cuz well you look at NASDAQ
it's way down I mean I'll be I'll
working over time
tonight oh wait wait wait what's there
we go you see it no do you see it no
who's
talking this guy it doesn't know attacks
from his
elbow are you talking to people at work
hey hey
tell him to quit uh horsing around at
his job Jack said quit horsing around
and he said job and air quotes tell Jack
I'm going to punch him in the goddamn
mouth wait I think this is ridiculous
what is this one here for why is this
one even in why hello what remote is it
there's like six remotes how
stupid so I'm sorry I'm sorry to
interrupt um I have a 430 with United
buttons with United buttons I'm going to
need you to stall Mr yoshii stall Mr
yoshiomi and I'm going to get on that is
Yoshi Toya no we have a to it's a
Toshiba no no it's a Toshiba Toshiba
it's a Toshiba not a toshima no Yoshi
mom ask him if there's a Blu-ray input
he wants to know a Blu-ray input cuz we
bought a Blu-ray player today you bought
a Blu-ray player yeah cuz you want to
watch Willow Willow came out on Blu-ray
you're going to watch our movie our
movie on a Blu-ray player without me
Willow man we made guac we got pizza
chips drinks you're a rat You're a Rat
Bastard well we'll we'll save some for
you I really don't I really don't have
time for
this tell them to plug things back in
where they were before press input four
and the cable should work if the
cable no it's proba yeah it's probably
broken it says it's broken yeah you guys
probably broke it idiots it's broken I'm
so mad I'm so mad you
guys
[Music]
I want you to like our
Channel And subscribe oh subscribe I
want you to like de
Kevin
[Music]
subscribe